pretome.net 2012-11-30

# Dove House - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Dove House. This statement describes our privacy practices for our website, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You can visit www.DoveHouse.us without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. However, access to certain portions of the website may require you to submit information such as user-id and password. If you wish for us to contact you, we will need some personal information such as your name, address, email and phone number.

To access our transaction programs, we may ask for your address and/or credit card information. When registering via the website, we may also ask you to choose a security question to answer. This required information is necessary for us to process the transactions, issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against credit card fraud, and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account.

**INFORMATION SECURITY AND QUALITY**

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of any personally identifiable information you may provide. Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.

**COOKIES**

We sometimes use cookies to collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better service. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may be stored on your system. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of sites may not function properly.

**DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES**

We will not share personal information with a third party unless we are required by law to do so.

**RETURN / REFUND POLICY**

Merchandise Sales: We offer a full refund or even exchange for merchandise purchases within 30 days of purchase date. After 30 days, all merchandise sales are final.

Event Ticket Sales: All event ticket sales are final.

Donations: Refunds are not offered for donations made to Dove House.

**SHIPPING POLICY**

Your item(s) will be shipped from Dove House within two days of purchase. We will determine the most efficient and cost effective shipping carrier for your order. The carriers that may be used are: U.S. Postal Service (USPS), United Parcel Service (UPS) or FedEx. We cannot ship to P.O. Boxes.

Shipping and Handling Costs: $9.00 will be added to your order for the shipment of one item; $15 for multiple items.

**CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION**

While little, if any of the Dove House website is directed towards children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

**LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**

Dove House website contains links to other web sites. Dove House is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of these sites.

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

This privacy statement was created and written on November 5th, 2010 and approved on 11/30/2010 by the Dove House Board of Directors. Please visit this page from time to time to check for updates.

**QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS STATEMENT**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Executive Director of the Dove House Children’s Advocacy Center at 704-883-9814.
